Come, sorrow. We welcome thee.
غم. ما thee مورد استقبال.
Let us join in grief,
ما اجازه بده غم همبسته بشويم.,
rejoice in despair,
در نوميدى شادماني بكن.,
and honor the fortunate dead.
و خوشبخت مرده.
Dearly beloved...
محبوب به گرانى...
[Cat Meows]
ميوهايى گربه
Shh!
Shh!
Tsk tsk tsk.
Tsk.
Good show, old man.
خوب man مسن.
Gomez.
Gomez.
Cara mia?
Mia?
Marvelous news.
خبر اعجاب انگيز.
I'm going to have a baby...
من دارم مىروم كه طفلى...
right now.
راست now.
Nurse, how close are the contractions?
نزديك انقباضات?
Every 15 seconds, Doctor.
Every ثانيه‌اى, دكتر.
Are you in unbearable pain?
آيا شما هستيد? درد تحمل ناپذيرى?
Is it inhuman? My darling, is it torture?
آيا آن غيرانسانى است? عزيز من, آن?
Oui.
Oui.
And then mommy kissed daddy,
و آنوقت mommy پدر بوسيده شده‌است.,
and the angel told the stork.
و فرشته لك لك.
The stork flew down from heaven
. زير آسمان
and left a diamond under a leaf in the cabbage patch,
و الماسى زير ورقى در تكه كلم ,
and the diamond turned into a baby.
و الماس توى طفلى.
Our parents are having a baby, too.
. طفلى.
They had sex.
آنها جنس داشتند.
Push, Mrs. Addams.
Addams.
[Moans Lightly]
بسبكى
Forceps!
انبر قابلگى!
Forceps.
.
Aah!
Aah!
Would you like anesthesia?
شما متمايل بود? بيهوشى?
No, thank you. But ask the children.
No. ولي كودكان را بپرست.
Cara mia.
Mia.
Mon cher.
Mon.
Mrs. Addams, the baby?
Addams
Pardon.
ببخشاي.
- It's a boy. - It's a girl.
- آن پسرى. - آن دخترى.
- Gomez! - What news?
- Gomez! - What چه?
Father, what is it?
Father., آيا آن what چه‌اى است?
It's an Addams!
آن Addams!
I've arranged a little surprise, my dearest.
من a little تعجبى آراسته‌ام., من عزيز.
I hope you like it.
من انتظار دارم شما آن متمايل هستيد.
Oh, Gomez, it's dark, it's depressing, it's desolate.
آن تاريكى, آن آن.
It says, "toddler."
آن تاتي كننده."
It's a dream.
آن رويايى.
Come, cara mia.
Mia.
The Addams cradle.
گهواره Addams.
Welcome home, my son.
خوشامد پسر من.
[Baby Laughs]
خنده‌هايى طفل
That's not true.
آن.
Everyone knows it is.
Everyone مىداند آن است.
When you have a new baby, one of the other children has to die.
شما طفل نويى دارد., يك از كودكان ديگر (defective verb) كه.
- Really? - It's a tradition. One of us has to go.
- واقعا? - آن سنتى. يك ما كه.
Which one?
Which?
Well, they only need one boy.
آنها تنها يك پسر.
He has my father's eyes.
او چشمهاى پدر من.
Gomez, take those out of his mouth.
Gomez آنها از دهان او.
Coochie coochie coo.
Coochie.
A baby in the house.
طفلى در خانه.
It's about time. Hey, kiddo.
آن در حدود. Hey.
Did you see that?
آيا شما آن ديديد?
He's a real devil.
او شيطان واقعىى.
Pugsley, the baby weighs 10 pounds.
Pugsley طفل حوض آب.
The cannonball weighs 20 pounds.
.
Which will hit the stone walkway first?
Which زد. گردشگاه stone اولا?
I'm still on fractions.
من خاموش بر بخشهايى.
Which do you think?
Which كدامى شما?
The cannonball?
گلوله توپ?
Very good. But which one will bounce?
خوب كاملا. ولي يك اراده?
The baby?
طفل?
There's only one way to find out.
آنجا يك تنها راه كه.
Ready?
آماده?
1...
1...
2...
2...
3.
3.
What a glorious evening.
What چه‌اى evening باشكوه.
Rain.
ببار.
Cara mia.
Mia.
Oh, dear.
Oh عزيز.
Children, why do you hate the baby?
كودكان., آيا شما طفل را متنفر هستيد چرا?
We just want to play with him.
ما تنها مىخواهيم. كه او.
Especially his head.
بخصوص.
Do you think we love the baby more than you?
آيا شما انديشه مىكنيد ما طفل را عاشق هستيم? شما?
- Yes.
- آرى.
Do you think when a new baby arrives,
شما طفل نويى مىرسد.,
another child has to die?
كودك. كه?
- Yes.
- آرى.
Well, that's just not true.
فوران بكن., آن دادگر.
Not anymore.
نه زيادتر.
It's just sibling rivalry.
آن دادگر رقابت.
Gomez, do you remember what we were like?
Gomez شما آيا ما بوديم what چه‌اى?
- I hated you! - I despised you.
- من شما متنفر بودم! - من شما تحقير كردم.
I choked him till he lost consciousness
من او خفه كردم. او آگاهى
and had to be put on a respirator.
و كه دستگاه تنفس مصنوعى.
I tied him to a tree
من او تا درختى به هم بستم.
and pulled out four of his permanent teeth.
و out از دندانهاى او جاودانى.
When he was asleep,
او خوابيده بود.,
I opened his skull and removed his brains.
من جمجمه‌ى او را باز كردم. و مغزهاى او را.
You did?
شما?
A brother!
برادرى!
Brother!
برادر!
Children, you see?
كودكان, شما?
"Death! Death to the enemies
"مرگ! Death. تا دشمنان
of the people of the republic."
از مردمان از جمهورى."
Hoorah!
Hoorah!
Justice is served.
دادگسترى به درد خورده مىشود.
Bring forward the evil one.
Forward One شرير.
[La Marseillaise Plays]
La Marseillaise
You have betrayed the people of France.
شما. مردمان از فرانسه.
You are evil incarnate.
شما شر.
How do you plead?
شما?
[Pugsley] Guilty.
Pugsley گناهكار.
Guilty by her own admission.
گناهكار پذيرش او اذعان بدار.
The sentence is death.
جمله death.
Executioner, place her on the block.
دژخيم., او بر توده جاى بده.
1...
1...
2...
2...
Children, what are you doing?
كودكان., شما what چه‌اى?
- Playing!
- !
3!
3!
Woe to the republic.
غصه تا جمهورى.
Look at you.
شما.
Midnight, moonlight,
نيمه شب moonlight,
surrounded by death.
Death.
It's been too long.
آن به طول too.
Do it! Hold him still!
آن! او هنوز!
[Gunshot, Glass Breaking]
زخم گلوله , Breaking
You missed.
شما خطا كرديد.
Here, catch!
اينجا!
I don't want him!
من او نمىخواهم!
[Glass Breaking]
Breaking
One house, three children.
يك خانه., كودكى.
So many windows.
چندين پنجره‌هايى.
My darling, it's you I'm worried about,
عزيز من, آن شما من نگران در حدود.,
the stress, all this squabbling.
, دارد ستيزه مىكند.
Oh, I'll be fine.
Oh من خوب بود.
I'm just like any modern woman, trying to have it all--
, All كه آن.--
loving husband, a family.
شوهر, خانواده‌اى.
It's just I wish I had more time
آن دادگر من خواست من more
to seek out the dark forces
كه زورها بي نور.
and join their hellish crusade, that's all.
و جهنمى همبسته بشو., آن همه.
You can! You shall! So it must be!
شما قوطي! شما! بنابراينى آن!
[Glass Breaking]
Breaking
But how?
ولي?
Children, as your new nanny,
كودكان., مثل پرستار شما نو,
I know that we're all concerned
من All اهميت داشته.
about the environment,
درباره محيط,
so this morning, let's discuss
بنابراينى this morning, We گفتگو بكنيم.
how to prevent forest fires.
كه حريقهايى جنگل.
Prevent them?
آنها?
All right, children,
به سمت راست همه كودكان,
I've had it up to here.
من آن. اينجا.
Now you just answer one simple question.
شما تنها اكنون پاسخ مىدهيد. يك پرسش آسانى.
Where is that baby?
آيا آن طفل است?
Which part?
Which كدامى?
Hello, kiddies.
سلام kiddies.
I'm Polly the puppet.
دست نشانده.
What shall we do today?
ما what چه‌اى امروز،اين روزها?
I know. Let's all clean our rooms.
من. We all اتاقهاى ما را.
Hello, Polly.
سلام Polly.
I'll clean my room
من اتاق من را پاك كرد.
in exchange for your immortal soul.
جان ياروان جاويد.
Hi. Addams residence?
Hi. اقامتگاه Addams?
Ooh, it's old.
Ooh آن مسن.
And big.
و بزرگ.
Lurch.
تلوتلو بخور.
Hi! Hi. I'm Debbie Jellinsky from the agency.
Hi! Hi. I از نمايندگى.
The agency?
نمايندگى?
But they claimed no one else was available.
ولي آنها No one else در دسترس نبود.
They suggested a Doberman.
آنها Doberman.
Surprise! I've been out of town.
! من شهرستان.
Are you the mom?
آيا شما مام هستيد?
I am Mrs. Addams.
من Addams هستم.
I love your dress. It's so tight.
من لباس شما را عاشق هستم. آن محكم.
Thank you.
.
Gomez.
Gomez.
I believe we may have a new nanny...
من اعتقاد دارم ما داشت. پرستار نويى...
Miss Jellinsky.
Jellinsky خطا بكن.
Deb.
Deb.
Isn't he a lady-killer?
او?
Acquitted.
تبرئه كرده.
I'll show you all my references
من شما نشان داد. All رجوعهاى من.
so you'll know I'm not a homicidal maniac.
بنابراينى شما دانست من مربوط يامتمايل به آدم كشىى.
- Of course you're not. - You're too young.
- البته. - شما جوان too.
Welcome to our home.
تا خانه‌ى ما خوشامد بگو.
There's a belfry, a swamp,
آنجا belfry, مردابى.,
and a dungeon down below.
و سياهچالى پايين زير.
- Cable? - Of course.
- ? - البته.
Debbie.
Debbie.
Oh, is that the little critter?
Oh آن Critter ناچيز?
Oh, no. This is our baby.
Oh no. اين طفل ما است.
He's adorable. He's perfect. What's his name?
او قابل پرستش. او. What چه‌اى نام او?
It was agony.
آن بود.
We went through all the usual baby names...
ما رفتيم. All نامهاى طفل...
Lucifer...
Lucifer...
Benito...
Benito...
Mao.
Mao.
Then we came to our senses,
پس ما آمديم. تا شعورهاى ما,
something a child could live with...
چيز مهم يا جالب كودكى ...
Pubert.
Pubert.
Pubert...
Pubert...
I like it.
من آن متمايل هستم.
It's filthy.
آن پليد.
May I?
May من?
Your dress, is it flammable?
لباس شما., آيا آن قابل اشتعال است?
You've had your shots--
شما تيرهاى شما را.--
measles, mumps, rabies?
بيمارى گوشك بيمارى هارى?
Oh, I just adore little babies.
Oh من تنها طفلهاى ناچيزى.
I just want to squeeze them till there's not a breath left
من تنها مىخواهم كه آنها. آنجا چپى نفس
in their tiny little bodies.
در تنهاى آنها ناچيز ريز.
Hello, Pubert.
سلام Pubert.
I love you.
من شما عاشق هستم.
[Knock On Door]
در
Children, this is Miss Jellinsky, our new nanny.
كودكان, اين Jellinsky, پرستار ما نو.
What do we say?
آيا ما what چه‌اى مىگويم?
Be afraid. Be very afraid.
ترسان. ترسان كاملا.
Look at you--
شما.--
all cooped up in this house with a new baby.
All در اين خانه با طفل نويى.
That's not easy, is it?
آن آسان, It?
No.
No.
Why, I bet sometimes
چرا I بعضى اوقات
you wish it was still just the two of you.
شما آن دادگر هنوز شما.
Or less.
يا كمترى.
Well, don't you worry.
شما.
Everything's going to be just fine.
. عزيمت كه.
I love them.
من آنها عاشق هستم.
Thing...
چيز...
stop that.
آن بييستان.
He likes you.
او شما متمايل است.
Heh heh heh heh.
Heh.
I'm good with my hands.
من خوب با دستان من.
What a wonderful family,
What چه‌اى خانواده‌ى شگرفى ,
although there's one fella I haven't met yet.
آنجا يك fella من هنوز ديدار نكرده‌ام.
Hi there, mister.
Hi آنجا آقا.
Your nephew?
پسر برادر?
My brother.
برادر من.
No!
No!
Fester, come out here.
., بيا.
He's very shy.
او خجالتى كاملا.
Fester, this is Miss Jellinsky, our new nanny.
اين Jellinsky, پرستار ما نو.
Hello, Fester.
سلام.
These Addams men, where do you find them?
اينها مردان Addams., آيا شما آنها مىيابيد?
It has to be damp.
آن كه خيس (defective verb).
I can't wait.
من صبر بكنم.
I'll start first thing tomorrow.
من اولا چيز فردا.
Why not tonight?
چرا امشب?
[Morticia] Good night, Debbie.
Morticia خوب Debbie.
Good night!
شب به خير!
Scream if you need anything.
شما هرچيز.
So we've hired Miss Jellinsky.
بنابراينى ما Jellinsky خطا بكن.
She's a gem, don't you think?
او جواهرى, آيا شما انديشه نمىكنيد?
She's perfect.
او.
Oh, Fester, I'm such a lucky man.
Oh, من مردى lucky.
I hope that someday you'll know the indescribable joy
من آن روزى شما دانست خوشى وصف ناپذير.
of having children
كودكان
and of paying someone else to raise them.
و someone else كه آنها.
First wouldn't I have to get married?
اولا من كه?
You're just a boy. There's plenty of time.
شما تنها پسرى. آنجا فراوانى از موقع.
You'll meet someone, someone very special,
شما كسى ديدار كرد., كسى مخصوصى كاملا.,
someone who won't press charges.
كسى. اتهاماتيى.
Oh, I'd like that.
Oh من آن متمايل بود.
You rascal.
شما رذل.
Oh, and what's this?
Oh و what چه‌اى اين?
- Mom.
- مام.
Tonight on America's Most Disgusting Unsolved Crimes,
امشب Most بزه‌هاى حل نشده‌اى تنفر آورى.,
we investigate the case of Ursula...
ما تحقيق مىكنيم. جعبه‌ى Ursula...
Carmen...
Carmen...
and Nadine--
و Nadine--
three very different women with one thing in common--
زن متفاوتى كاملا. با يك چيز --
murder!
!
And they're all the same woman.
و آنها all. زن.
She's known by the police as the Black Widow.
او اداره شهربانى دانسته بيوه زن سياه.
She mates, then she kills.
او جفت مىشود., پس او مىكشد.
She investigates wealthy men,
او تحقيق مىكند. مردان توانگرى.,
finding the richest, loneliest bachelors,
دارا., مردمجردان تنهايى.,
gaining their trust and their love,
اطمينان آنها را. و عشق آنها,
and finally, she marries them.
و سرانجام , او آنها ازدواج مىكند.
Then, on the wedding night, she kills them.
آنوقت بر شب عروسي , او آنها مىكشد.
The deaths appear accidental.
Death. اتفاقى پديدار بشو.
After the funeral, she disappears, cash in hand,
مراسم دفن , او,
but the money never lasts.
ولي پول هرگز ماندگار است.
Soon the Black Widow is hungry again,
بزودى بيوه زن سياه گرسنه از نو,
hungry for cash, hungry for love.
گرسنه پول نقد , گرسنه براي عشق.
A mistress of disguise, she's eluded the authorities for years.
خانمى , او مقاماتها را براي سالهايى.
Who is she,
آيا او است.,
and what seemingly innocent pose will she next assume?
و what چه‌اى ظاهرا ژست بي گناه Will او نزديك?
All we can say is...
All ما...
bachelors, beware.
مردمجردان,.
We'll be going out for most of the morning.
ما رفت. Most از بامداد.
All the important numbers--
All عددهاى مهم.--
police, fire department, morgue.
بخش حريق, .
Fester, come along.
Along.
Goodbye, Fester.
خداحافظ.
Say goodbye to Debbie.
خداحافظ Debbie.
[Mumbles Nervously]
باعصبانيت
Have fun!
سرگرمى!
[Door Closes]
پايانهايى در
Mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm!
Mmm-mmm-mmm-mmm!
Fester Addams. My, my.
Addams. من من.
Stocks and bonds...
ذخيره‌هايى و بستگىهايى...
deeds...
سندهايى...
gold bullion.
شمش طايى.
Treasury bills...
...
IRAs.
IRAs.
What a strange old house.
What چه‌اى خانه‌ى مسنى غريبى.
It's so drafty.
آن.
It's really no place for children.
آن واقعا no براي كودكان.
No place at all.
No محلى all.
Hold still, you little brat.
هنوز., شما بچه لوس ناچيز.
He's not a brat.
او بچه لوس.
Of course not. He's an adorable little baby.
البته. او طفل ناچيزى قابل پرستشى.
Fine. Rub it in.
جريمه بكن. آن in .
We're getting him all ready
ما داريم او به دست مىآوريم. آماده همه
for a nice little walk.
براي گردش ناچيزى خوبى.
Would you like to come?
شما متمايل بود كه?
Are you really a nanny?
شما واقعا پرستارى?
What a question.
What چه‌اى پرسشى.
Why did you come here?
آيا شما اينجا آمديد چرا?
Why, to take care of you...
چرا كه شما...
all of you.
All شما.
Especially my uncle?
بخصوص عموى من?
I shouldn't be telling you this.
من. شما اين.
They swore me to secrecy,
آنها من سوگند خوردند. تا اختفا ,
the little angels,
فرشته‌هاى ناچيز.,
but they want to go.
ولي آنها مىخواهند كه.
It's all they talked about all morning.
آن همه آنها All بامداد.
They're just afraid to ask you.
آنها ترسان تنها. كه شما.
They're afraid you'll think they don't love you.
آنها ترسان شما انديشه كرد. آنها شما عاشق نيستند.
The poor things.
چيزهاى بي پول.
It's a bizarre request.
آن تقاضاى غيرمانوسى.
It's horrifying.
آن.
They have their hearts set on it.
آنها قلبهاى آنها را دارند. بر آن مستقر بشو.
I knew you'd want to know
من شما خواست كه.
as concerned, caring parents.
اهميت داشته , دارند پرستارى مىكنند.
Oh, Gomez, what shall we do?
., ما what چه‌اى?
How can we say no?
ما no?
Don't even mention it.
آن حتى ذكر نكن.
Just do it.
آن تنها.
I'm sure they'll deny everything,
من مطمئن. آنها همه چيز انكار كرد.,
but they want to go,
ولي آنها مىخواهند كه.,
God love them.
يزدان آنها.
- Summer camp.
- اردو بزن صيف.
"Camp Chippewa."
"Chippewa اردو بزن."
How charming.
فريبنده.
What's a chippewa?
What چه‌اى chippewa?
It's an old Indian word.
آن مسن Word.
It means orphan.
آن وسيله.
Fresh air...
آهنگ بانشاط...
the scent of pine.
بو از كاج.
[Morticia] Wednesday, look at all of the other children--
Morticia Wednesday, All از كودكان ديگر.--
their freckles, their bright little eyes,
., چشمهاى آنها ناچيز روشن.,
their eager, friendly smiles.
آنها مشتاق , لبخندهاى دوستانه‌اى.
Help them.
آنها كمك بكن.
Hi. I'm Amanda Buckman.
Hi. I.
Why are you dressed like that?
آيا شما لباس پوشانده مىشود چرا. آن?
Like what?
What چه‌اى مانند?
Like you're going to a funeral.
مراسم دفن.
Why are you dressed like somebody died?
آيا شما لباس پوشانده مىشود چرا. كسى?
Wait.
صبر بكن.
Hi. Don Buckman.
Hi. Buckman.
Isn't this place something else?
Something else?
Very exclusive.
انحصارى كاملا.
A kid has to be extra special to get in,
بچه‌اى كه (defective verb). مخصوص بطور اضافى كه,
gifted, exceptional.
با استعداد استثنايى.
Our Amanda's already skipped two grades.
تاحالا درجه‌اى.
How about your boy?
درباره پسر شما?
Probation.
.
We just love Chippewa.
ما Chippewa تنها عاشق هستيم.
Amanda couldn't wait.
Amanda صبر بكند.
It's all she talked about.
آن همه او در حدود حرف زد.
She's got a whole new wardrobe.
او نويى درستى.
And this little lady?
و اين بانوى ناچيز?
Wednesday's at that very special age
آن پيرى مخصوص كاملا.
when a girl has only one thing on her mind.
دخترى. يك تنها چيز بر ذهن او.
Boys?
پسران?
Homicide.
آدمكشى.
[Whistle Blows]
وزشهايى
Attention!
توجه!
Hey! Listen up, everybody.
Hey! , هركس.
I'm Gary Granger!
من!
And I'm Becky Martin-Granger.
و .
We're the owners and directors here at Camp Chippewa,
ما دارندگان و مديران. اينجا Chippewa,
America's foremost facility for...
پيشترين آسانى...
privileged young adults.
بزرگسالان جوانى داراى امتيازى.
And we're all here to learn, to grow,
و ما اينجا همه. كه كه,
and to just plain have fun!
و ساده تنها سرگرمى!
'Cause that's what being privileged is all about.
'آن what چه داراى امتياز all در حدود.
Buffy!
Buffy!
How are you?
آيا شما هستيد?
I'm fine.
من خوب.
How are you doing?
شما?
I don't think I like it here.
من انديشه نمىكنم. من آن اينجا متمايل هستم.
Do you know how dirty you are?
شما شما?
Please leave him alone.
او به تنهايى لطفا رها بكن.
I can't breathe.
من تنفس بكنم.
Stand up straight, please.
بالايى سرراست, دلپذير بباش.
This is why he's always sick.
اين چرا او بيمار هميشه.
Don't start with me.
من.
This has nothing to do with allergies.
اين nothing كه با حساسيتهايى.
You did this.
شما اين.
Can you breathe?
شما تنفس بكنيد?
Stand up straight.
بالايى سرراست.
"Everyone at the ball
"Everyone در توپ.
"turned and stared at Cinderella.
"و Cinderella.
"Who is that beautiful woman? everyone asked.
"آيا آن زن خوشگل است? Everyone پرسيده.
"Even Prince Charming noticed the new arrival.
"شاهزاده‌ى تراز فريبنده ورود نو.
"Who are you? he asked Cinderella.
"آيا شما هستيد? او Cinderella پرسيد.
[Creak]
Creak
"My name is Cinderella, she said to the prince.
"نام من Cinderella است., او تا شاهزاده.
"Could you tell me
"شما من بگويد?
"who is that man over by the punch bowl,
"آيا آن man است. تمام نزديك مشت ,
"that fascinating man,
"آن man.,
"that oddly sensual man,
"آن man شهوانى به طرز غيرعادى.,
"that man who makes me quiver under my bodice,
"آن مرد كه من مىسازد. Bodice.,
that baldman?"
آن baldman?"
She's driving me wild!
او من وحشى!
Who?
?
Debbie.
Debbie.
Even the sound of her name...
صدا حتى. از نام او...
Debbie.
Debbie.
Isn't it beautiful?
آن خوشگل?
She makes me think of vinyl. Chemicals!
او من مىسازد انديشه بكنم. ماده شيميايى!
Truly, Fester,
صادقانه.,
has it finally happened, at long last?
آيا آن سرانجام روى داده‌است?, به طول?
I don't know. I think so.
من don نمىدانم. من انديشه مىكنم بنابراينى.
All these years I've watched you and Morticia
All اينها سالها. من شما و Morticia مراقب بوده‌ام.
through windows, doorways,
ازميان پنجره‌هايى, درگاه‌هايى.,
keyholes.
.
I've been so happy for you,
من شاد. شما ,
but I have to confess I've been jealous, too.
ولي من (defective verb) كه. من حسود.
I've dreamed that sometime
من خواب ديده‌ام. آن كاه بيگاه
there might be someone for me.
آنجا كسى من.
There's Thing.
آنجا چيز.
I know, but I want more--
من, ولي من مىخواهم.--
legs, elbows,
پاها,,
a head.
سرى.
Two legs?
پايى?
Dare I ask Debbie to dinner?
من Debbie بپرستم? شام?
What if she says no?
What چه‌اى او no?
What if she says yes?
What چه‌اى او بله
If I asked her, would you come,
من او پرسيد., شما آمد?,
you and Morticia?
شما و Morticia?
Of course.
البته.
[Tweet]
Tweet
Life saving.
اندوخته زندگي.
We're all top-notch swimmers.
ما all. شناگران عالىى.
Now we show our stuff
ما جنس ما را اكنون نشان مىدهيم.
and earn those certificates.
و آنها گواهىها.
How about our first little pair
در حدود Pair ناچيز.
of life saving buddies?
از رفيقهايى اندوخته زندگي?
Amanda, Wednesday.
Amanda Wednesday.
Is that your bathing suit?
آن ?
Is that your over bite?
آن شما بيش از?
One of you will be the drowning victim.
يك شما بود. قربانى غرق.
The other one will be our lifesaver.
One ديگر. نعمت ما بود.
I'll be the victim.
من قربانى بود.
All your life.
همه زندگي شما.
I'm going to be an actress.
من دارم كه مىروم. .
Brava!
Brava!
Now jump in, swim out a few yards,
اكنون بپران., A few شنا بكن.,
and start drowning.
و.
Help me!
من كمك بكن!
I'm drowning!
من دارم غرق مىكنم!
I'm dying!
من دارم مىميرم!
I can't swim.
من شنا بكنم.
[Playing A Tango]
نوعى رقص آرام (تانگو)
It's our favorite bistro.
آن ميخانه كوچك محبوب.
We've been coming here for years.
ما آينده اينجا. براي سالهايى.
Of course, it has been redone.
البته , آن دوباره انجام داده شده‌است.
Oh, it's just...
Oh آن دادگر...
lovely.
دوست داشتنى.
Isn't it, Fester?
آن)
Fester.
.
[Muffled]
خاموش كرده
It's a quaint French custom--
آن شگفت و جالب عادت.--
sharing half-eaten bread.
نان - تاحدى خورده شده‌است.
Fester is truly continental.
چرك صادقانه قاره اى.
He spent many years abroad.
او چندين سالهايى خارج.
He speaks 12 languages fluently.
او زبانى بيان مىكند. به فصاحت.
I could tell.
من بگوم.
When I first saw him,
من اولا او,
I thought he was from Europe.
من انديشه كردم. او از اروپا بود.
You did?
شما?
It's true.
آن.
But I took a bath.
ولي من bath.
Fester's really a wonderful man.
چرك واقعا مرد شگرفى.
He's just terribly shy.
او دادگر خجالتى به طرز وحشتناك.
I just can't tell--
من بگوم تنها.--
does he like me at all?
آيا او من متمايل است? به هيچوجه?
Of course he does.
البته او.
He vomited.
او بالا آورد.
Does he always do that with women he likes?
او آن هميشه? با زنهايى او?
Oh, no.
Oh no.
Just you.
دادگر شما.
Ah.
Ah.
Do you think she minded?
آيا شما انديشه مىكنيد او مواظبت كرد?
Of course not.
البته.
She adores you.
او شما مىپرستد.
I'm making such a mess of things.
من تركيب. از چيزهايى.
Gomez, how do you do it?
Gomez شما آن?
How can I be like you?
من شما?
How can I be suave?
من با نزاكت?
Woo her, admire her,
او او,
make her feel like she's the most sublime creature on Earth.
او او Most آفريده‌ى بر زمين والا.
Yes. That's it?
آرى. آن it?
We're back,
ما پس.,
noses powdered.
بينىهايى.
Perfection achieved.
كمال. دست يافته.
We are the luckiest brothers on Earth.
ما luckiest هستيم. برادران بر زمين.
We are unworthy of such splendor,
ما ناشايسته هستيم. Splendor,
undeserving of such radiance.
Undeserving. از تابندگى.
Uh, that's right.
Uh آن راست.
We should have... ugly girls.
ما داشت... دخترهاى زشتى.
[Violin Plays]
بازىهايى ويولن
[Gasp]
نفس بريده
[Muffled] Hah!
خاموش كرده Hah!
And then the ghost said,
و آنوقت شبح گفته.,
"And I will haunt you forever."
"و من will شما جاودانه."
- Ooh.
- Ooh.
Wednesday,
Wednesday.,
you have to continue the ghost story.
شما (defective verb) كه. قصه شبح.
This is dumb.
اين گنگ است.
Well, if you can't do it...
شما آن...
And, so, the next night,
و بنابراينى شب نزديك ,
the ghost returned to the haunted cabin,
شبح. كلبه,
and he said to the campers,
و او Camper,
"None of you really believe in me,
"هيچى شما. من واقعا اعتقاد بدار.,
so I'll have to prove my power."
بنابراينى من داشت كه نيروى من را."
And the next morning,
و بامداد نزديك ,
when the campers woke up,
Camper,
all of their old noses had grown back.
All از بينىهاى آنها مسن. پس.
- Aah!
- Aah!
Oh, Fester,
Oh,
how you must hate me.
شما من.
What?
What چه‌اى?
Here you are,
اينجا شما ,
a debonair man of the world.
خوشخو مرد از جهان.
How I must bore you.
من شما خسته بشوم.
Oh, never.
Oh هرگز.
Fester, before we go any further,
قبلا ما نه بيشتر مىرويم.,
I have a confession,
من اقرارى دارم.,
something I must tell you.
. من شما بگوم.
I'm a virgin.
من.
You are?
شما?
Yes.
آرى.
What's that?
What چه‌اى آن?
It--It's someone
كسى It--It.
who's never experienced physical love.
هرگز تجربه كرده عشق جسمانى.
Oh.
Oh.
You mean, with another person.
شما , با كس.
Then, Debbie,
آنوقت Debbie,
I have a confession to make, as well.
من اقرارى دارم.
I'm one, too.
من يك.
You? You?
شما? شما?
Yes.
آرى.
But with your looks, your charm,
ولي شما , افسون شما.,
women must follow you everywhere.
زنهايى شما درهرجا پيروى بكن.
Store detectives.
كارآگاگان انبار بكن.
Oh, Fester,
Oh,
I always dreamed
من هميشه خواب ديدم.
of meeting someone untouched,
كسى دست نخورده‌اى.,
someone pure,
كسى ناب ,
someone... just like you.
كسى... شما تنها متمايل بباش.
You'll meet him.
شما او ديدار كرد.
And--And I dreamed that when I met him,
And--And من آن من او,
that we would wait until our wedding night
ما صبر كرد. تا شب ما عروسي
to give ourselves to one another,
كه we. يكديگر,
to make the ultimate sacrifice.
كه فداكارى آخرين.
A goat?
بزى?
Until now I thought it was impossible,
من now انديشه كردم. آن غير ممكن بود.,
but, Fester Addams,
ولي Addams,
I love you.
من شما عاشق هستم.
You do?
شما?
Please, I have to know how you feel about me.
من كه شما من در حدود احساس مىكند.
I love you.
من شما عاشق هستم.
I worship you.
من شما عبادت مىكنم.
I'd do anything for you.
من هرچيز شما.
I'd pay.
من پرداخت كرد.
Fester!
!
Debbie!
Debbie!
Oh.
Oh.
Look at him.
او.
So peaceful.
آرام.
This evening as I watched Fester and Debbie,
This evening. من چرك و Debbie,
I kept my fingers crossed.
من انگشتان من تقاطع كردند.
I hoped...
من انتظار داشتم...
I prayed.
من.
Let them fall in love.
آنها اجازه بده. در عشق پائين بيا.
Let them know happiness.
آنها اجازه بده سعادت بدانند.
Let them adopt.
آنها اجازه بده اتخاذ بكنند.
Gomez, Morticia,
.,
great news--
خبر كلان.--
Something impossible, a miracle.
غير ممكنى., معجزه‌اى.
- The rash... - It's gone.
- كهير... - آن.
I'm engaged.
من درگير.
That ring...
آن حلقه...
It was our mother's. She was buried with it.
آن بود. او با آن به خاك سپرده شد.
[Thunder]
تندر
Mail call.
صدا زره.
Addams.
Addams.
Barkley, Castleman, Calloway,
Barkley., .,
Finley, Fisher, Framingham...
Framingham...
Oh, no.
Oh no.
What is it?
آيا آن what چه‌اى است?
This is unspeakable.
اين توصف نشدنى است.
Is something wrong? Bad news?
آيا اشتباه است? خبر بد?
It's the worst thing ever in the history of human events.
آن چيز بدترين هميشه در تاريخ از پيشامدهاى انسانىى.
Uncle Fester is getting married.
چرك عمو. ازدواج كرده.
A wedding?
عروسيى?
But that's great news.
ولي آن خبر كلان.
To whom?
?
The nanny.
پرستار.
Get out of the cabin.
از كلبه به دست بآور.
I'd kill myself.
من خودم كشت.
The help?
امداد?
I'm sure she's a very nice lady.
من مطمئن. او بانوى خوبى كاملا.
I think that's disgusting.
من انديشه مىكنم. آن.
Their whole family's
.
like some weird medical experiment.
غريب برخى متمايل بباش. تجربه‌ى طبى.
I think they're like circus people.
من انديشه مىكنم آنها. مردمان سيرك متمايل بباش.
What did you say?
آيا شما what چه‌اى گفتيد?
Tempers.
خوهايى.
Group hug.
بغل گروه.
Wednesday.
Wednesday.
Pugsley.
Pugsley.
Will a hug hurt us?
بغلى ما صدمه ديد?
We don't hug.
ما don بغل نمىكنيم.
Oh, they're just shy.
Oh خجالتى تنها.
We're not shy.
ما خجالتى.
We're contagious.
ما واگيردار.
I'm sensing some friction here,
من sensing. برخى اصطكاكى اينجا ,
something not quite Chippewa.
. به تمامى Chippewa.
- Mm-hmm.
- Mm-hmm.
Hey, no problem-o.
Hey.
All they need are good friends, good fun,
All آنها دوستان خوبى, سرگرمى خوبى,
and a little time in the harmony hut.
و موقع ناچيزى در كلبه هم آهنگي.
How long do we have to stay in here?
ما. كه?
[Door Opens]
در
Have fun.
سرگرمى.
What are you in for?
What چه‌اى شما در?
I wouldn't go horseback riding.
من رفت. Horseback.
That's all?
آن همه?
And I wouldn't make a bird house.
و من خانه‌اى پرنده بساز.
Why not?
چرا?
I just wanted to read.
من تنها خواستم كه.
Not on my time, four-eyes.
بر موقع من, Four-eyes.
Aah!
Aah!
Hurry up.
عجله بكن.
I'm coming.
من آينده.
Wait.
صبر بكن.
Be careful.
Careful.
Tetanus.
كزاز.
[Siren]
آژير
There they are!
آنجا آنها!
I saw them sneak out.
من آنها ديدم. .
What do you think you're doing?
What چه‌اى شما شما?
We have to see our family.
ما (defective verb) كه. خانواده‌ى ما.
It's important.
آن مهم.
More important than summer fun?
مهم سرگرمى صيف?
than making new friends?
دوستان نويى?
More important than sharing?
مهم ?
Joel Glicker, I'm surprised at you.
., من غافلگيرشده شما.
I have to get out of here.
من Out اينجا.
I have allergies.
من حساسيتهايى دارم.
Oh, you're allergic?
Oh?
To sunshine, archery, and crafts?
تا آفتاب , كماندارى, و پيشه‌هايى?
Yes.
آرى.
I think they should be punished.
من انديشه مىكنم. آنها تنبيه كرده بشوند.
Punished! Punished!
تنبيه كرده! تنبيه كرده!
No! We are not here to punish.
No! ما اينجا نيستيم. كه.
We are here to inspire.
ما اينجا كه.
Know what our little ninja friends need?
What چه‌اى ما ناچيز دوستان ninja?
Know what might turn their sad, wasted lives around?
بدان. زندگيهاى آنها پيرامون?
What?
What چه‌اى?
[Guitar Strums]
Strum
♪ Kumbaya, my Lord ♪
~ Kumbaya من خدا  ~
♪ Kumbaya ♪
~ Kumbaya. ~
[Wolf Howls]
زوزه‌هايى wolf
♪ Kumbaya, my Lord ♪
~ Kumbaya من خدا  ~
♪ Kumbaya ♪
~ Kumbaya. ~
♪ Oh, Lord, Kumbaya ♪♪
~ Oh Kumbaya ~~
Now, Debbie, have you met everyone?
Now Debbie, آيا شما everyone ديدار كرده‌ايد?
Morticia.
Morticia.
Margaret.
Margaret.
[Kiss Kiss]
بوس بوس
Margaret, this is our bride-to-be.
Margaret اين Bride-to-be.
Welcome to our family.
خوشامد بگو. تا خانواده‌ى ما.
I can't tell you what it's meant
من شما بگوم. What چه‌اى آن قصد داشته
joining the Addams clan.
. طايفه Addams.
Have you met my husband Cousin Itt?
آيا شما شوهر من را ديدار كرده‌ايد? دخترعمو Itt?
We've been so happy,
ما شاد.,
and, just as little Pubert arrived,
و ناچيز as تنها Pubert رسيد.,
we were blessed with our own little bundle of joy.
ما تاييد كرده were بسته‌ى ما مال خود ناچيز از خوشى.
What?
What چه‌اى?
Oh, I didn't say anything.
Oh من هرچيز didn نگفتم.
That's the baby's nickname-- What?
آن طفل What چه‌اى?
From the obstetrician.
.
Isn't he precious?
او گرانبها?
We've had offers.
ما پيشنهاداتيى.
♪ For he's a jolly good fellow ♪
~ او شخص خوبى شاد وسرزنده‌اى. ~
♪ Which nobody can deny ♪♪
~ Which كدام ~~
You guys are the best bunch of friends
شما مردان بهترين از دوستان
a fella could hope for.
Fella انتظار بدارد.
What a party!
What چه‌اى حزبى!
And now for the piece de resistance.
و now تكه پايداري.
Ta-da!
Ta-da!
That poor girl.
آن دختر بي پول.
Lurch, was she in there before you baked?
دام, او شما قبلا?
[Groan]
Groan
So, so, so.
بنابراينى بنابراينى بنابراينى.
C'est la vie.
La.
[Laughter]
خنده
Ha ha ha ha!
Ha!
Are you really allergic?
آيا شما مبتلا به حساسيت واقعا هستيد?
Uh-huh.
Huh.
To almost everything.
تقريبا همه چيز.
No, you're not.
No.
Am, too.
.
I can't have dairy products
من داشت. محصولاتيى لبنيات.
or wear wool
يا پشم بپوش.
or drink fluoridated water.
يا بنوش. آب.
You know what happens
شما What چه‌اى روى مىدهد.
if my mom uses a fabric softener?
مام من ماده نرم كننده?
What?
What چه‌اى?
I die.
من مىميرم.
Where are you?
آيا شما هستيد?
Over here.
.
Where?
?
By the skeleton.
نزديك اسكلت.
I got your message inside my cutlet.
من پيام شما را به دست آوردم. Inside كتلت من.
I need to ask you something.
من نياز دارم كه شما. .
What?
What چه‌اى?
Do you believe in the existence of evil?
آيا شما اعتقاد داريد? در وجود از شر?
Well, did you meet my mom?
شما مام من?
My Uncle Fester's about to get married
. در حدود كه
to this woman in a white uniform.
تا اين زن لباس يكسان سفيدى.
A radiologist.
پرتوشناسى.
A nanny.
پرستارى.
I have to go to the wedding.
من (defective verb) كه. تا عروسي.
I have a pass. Want to come?
من پروانه‌اى دارم. كه?
You mean like... on a date?
شما... بر تاريخى?
No.
No.
I'd love to.
من عاشق بود.
[Plays "Sunrise, Sunset']
طلوع آفتاب غروب آفتاب
[Plays "Wedding March']
عروسي ماه مارچ
[Speaking Gibberish]
Gibberish
I,
من.,
Fester Addams,
Addams.,
do hereby declare my unending love.
بدين وسيله اعلام بكن. عشق من بي پايان.
I will worship you forever.
من شما جاودانه عبادت كرد.
I will devote...
من will...
my every waking moment
Every دم من دارد بيدار مىكند.
to your happiness alone.
تا سعادت شما به تنهايى.
Oh.
Oh.
Henceforth, I am your eternal
, من شما جاودانى
and helpless slave.
و برده‌ى بيچاره.
Nice.
Nice.
Ditto.
Ditto.
You're going to have a wonderful life together.
شما كه زندگي شگرف باهم.
Yes, I am.
آرى, من.
Come, darling,
عزيز,
let's see who's the next happy bride.
We عروس شاد نزديك.
Here, Debbie!
اينجا Debbie!
- To me! - Me!
- من!
Oh, I have it!
Oh من آن!
- No! I have it! - It's mine!
- No! من آن دارم! - آن!
Now you have to get married.
Now شما كه ازدواج كرده.
It's not binding.
آن الزام آور.
Tramp.
پياده برو.
- Bye! - Congratulations!
- Bye! - تبريكهايى!
- Bon voyage!
- Bon!
The key ingredient
كليدى.
to a successful Hawaiian honeymoon
كامياب وابسته به ايالت هاوايى.
is romantic music.
موسيقي عاشقانه واحساسىى.
[Romantic Music Plays]
بازىهاى عاشقانه واحساسىى موسيقي
I ordered this cassette from Time-Life.
من اين مقرر داشتم. Time-Life.
5,000 of the World's Most Romantic Melodies.
5, Most آهنگهاى عاشقانه واحساسىى.
It's superb.
آن عالى.
What do you call this?
What چه‌اى شما. اين?
Number 438.
عدد. 438.
So...
بنابراينى...
do you like romantic living?
شما زندگى عاشقانه واحساسىى?
I do, so far.
من دور.
I love romantic living.
من زندگى عاشقانه واحساسىى عاشق هستم.
Oh, Fester, how much do you love me?
Oh آيا شما من عاشق هستيد?
With all my soul.
All جان ياروان.
Would you do anything for me?
شما? هرچيز من?
Anything.
هرچيز.
Would you die for me?
شما من مرد?
Yes.
آرى.
Promise?
?
Aah!
Aah!
Pumpkin?
كدو تنبل?
Muffin.
.
[TVPlays]
TVPlays
Darling, I know you're nervous.
عزيز, من شما عصبى.
So am I.
بنابراينى I .
I'm not nervous.
من عصبى.
I'm upset.
من آشفته مىشوم.
Because of the bathtub?
وان حمام?
Th-Th--
Th-Th.--
That was an accident.
آن تصادفى بود.
I know.
من.
I'm fine.
من خوب.
Don't give it another thought.
آن Don نده فكر.
Don't be frightened.
وحشت زده.
This is as new to me as it is to you.
اين نو as من آن شما.
Have you really never had sex?
شما واقعا. جنس هرگز?
Never.
هرگز.
Then how do you know we're not having it right now?
آنوقت شما آن اكنون به سمت راست?
We'll be just like Gomez and Morticia.
ما بود تنها Gomez و Morticia.
Pretend we're at home in my room--
تظاهر بكن ما. در اتاق من--
Granny down the hallway,
Granny تالا‌ر ورودى ,
Lurch by the door.
در تلوتلو بخور.
Oh, my God.
Oh من يزدان.
Please, what is it?
آن?
What do you need?
آيا شما what چه‌اى نياز داريد?
Only you, my dearest.
يگانه شما من عزيز.
Really?
واقعا?
Fester, I'm ready.
.
- Just one thing... - Gomez told me. No giggling.
- يك تنها چيز... - Gomez من گفت. No.
- And? - No hand puppets.
- و? - No به دست كسى نمىدهند.
- And... - What?
- و... - What چه‌اى?
after we've made love,
ما عشق ,
you can never see your family again.
شما هرگز ببينيد. خانواده‌ى شما از نو.
What?
What چه‌اى?
Otherwise, I could never really enjoy myself.
در غير اين صورت من هرگز خودم واقعا.
I could never give myself completely.
من هرگز خودم كاملا.
Unless I never see my family again?
مگر من هرگز مىبينم خانواده‌ى من از نو?
Yes. If I picture them in our lives,
آرى. من آنها مجسم مىكند. در زندگيهاى ما,
I could never achieve... you know.
من هرگز دست بيابم... شما.
Never?
هرگز?
Don't you love me?
آيا شما من عاشق نيستيد?
Of course.
البته.
Don't you want me?
آيا شما من نمىخواهيد?
Yes.
آرى.
Never.
هرگز.
Stud.
قبه.
Whoa!
Whoa!
Uh...
Uh...
ahh...
Ahh...
It's so odd we haven't heard from Fester and Debbie.
آن عجيب ما haven نشنيده‌ايم چرك و Debbie.
It's been almost a week. Hasn't it, little fellow?
آن تقريبا هفته‌اى. It شخص ناچيز?
Look at him.
او.
Too much fun at that reception.
Much سرگرمىى. در آن پذيرايى.
Hair of the pup.
مو.
Excellent, Amanda!
عالى Amanda!
Thank you.
.
Next!
نزديك!
[Wednesday] "Dear Wednesday and Pugsley,
Wednesday "Wednesday عزيز و Pugsley.,
"I love you dearly,
"من شما به گرانى عاشق هستم.,
but I can never see you again."
ولي من قوطي هرگز شما از نو ببين."
Glicker, go!
Glicker!
[Becky] Good try!
Becky خوب!
"When you are grown-up and very lonely,
"شما بالغ است. و تنها كاملا ,
"you'll understand.
"شما در يافت.
Love, Uncle Fester."
عشق)."
He's a dead man.
او مرد مرده‌اى.
Go!
برو!
[Bird Squawks]
جيغهايى پرنده
It's an American bald eagle!
آن آمريكايى عقاب طاس!
But aren't they extinct?
ولي آنها ازبين رفته?
They are now.
آنها اكنون.
Mrs. Addams?
Addams?
Yes?
بله?
Your hearse. Where's the body?
. ?
Right there.
راست آنجا.
But he's alive.
ولي او زنده.
Tell me about it!
من درباره آن بگو!
Fester, we may be together for a while...
ما باهم براي لحظه‌اى...
All our lives, cara mia.
All زندگيهاى ما., Mia.
What?
What چه‌اى?
Mon cher.
Mon.
- Speak English. - Pumpkin?
- انگليسى بيان بكن. - كدو تنبل?
If I have to be seen with you, we need to make some changes.
من كه ديدهشده شما (defective verb)., ما نياز داريم كه برخى تغييراتيى.
Changes?
?
Be careful! It's a credenza!
Careful! آن credenza!
These are beautiful things.
اينها چيزهاى خوشگلى.
They're from catalogues.
از فهرستهايى.
Fester, get over here!
., به دست بآور!
It itches.
آن مىخارد.
Don't touch it, not until the scab falls off.
آن دست نزن., پوست زخم off.
Pumpkin, do you think these clothes are really me?
كدو تنبل شما اينها رختها واقعا من?
Of course not. That's the point.
البته. آن نوك.
- Where do you want this? - The second floor boudoir.
- آيا شما اين مىخواهيد? - .
I'm her husband.
من شوهر او.
Fester!
!
Give me a kiss.
من بده.
Give me a 20. Watch it!
من 20. آن مراقب بباش!
That's a Queen Anne chandelier!
آن Anne چلچراغ!
"Hawaii is wonderful.
"هاوايى شگرف است.
"I wish you were here,
"من شما اينجا ,
"and I can never see you again!
"و من قوطي هرگز شما از نو ببين!
P.S., Debbie says hi."
Hi مىگود."
I don't understand. For weeks not a word, and now this.
من در نمىيابم. براي هفته‌هايى word و now اين.
Darling, come to bed. He can't be serious.
عزيز, تا بستر. او جدى.
Have I done something, said something?
من?, چيز مهم يا جالب?
Why does my brother despise me?
چرا برادر من من?
He adores you.
او شما مىپرستد.
I'd do anything for him.
من هرچيز او.
At his request, I would rip out my eyes.
در تقاضاى او, من out چشمهاى من.
At his command, I would crawl on my belly
فرمان بده., من بر شكم من خزيد.
through hot coals and broken glass.
داغ و شيشه‌ى شكسته شده‌است.
Why wait?
چرا?
Has Fester gone mad?
آيا چرك ديوانه رفته‌است?
This is all just some sort of phase.
اين دادگر همه است. برخى.
Post-honeymoon malaise.
ناراحتى.
It's very common.
آن عمومى كاملا.
Do you remember our honeymoon?
آيا شما به ياد مىآوريد? ماه عسل?
That glorious cruise.
آن باشكوه.
No quarrels.
No نزاع نمىكند.
No cares.
No پرستارى نمىكند.
No survivors.
No داراى توانايى بقاء.
Cara mia.
Mia.
So...
بنابراينى...
you still desire me after all these years?
شما من هنوز مىخواهيد. بعد از all اينها سالها?
The old ball and chain?
توپ مسن و?
Forever.
جاودانه.
I'll get them.
من آنها به دست آورد.
Heads up, campers. Thejamboree's only two weeks away.
Heads camper. دور تنها هفته‌ى Thejamboree.
And you know what that means-- clean cabins.
و شما آن what چه‌اى قصد دارد مىدانيد.-- كلبه‌هايى پاك بكن.
Creating with clay and...
با سفال و...
Canoes, canoes, canoes!
نوعى قايق
So we better get cracking, huh?
بنابراينى ما Cracking
Look at this. I've got them.
اين. من آنها به دست آورده‌ام.
Schizos and Serial Killers.
Schizos و آدمكشهاى دنباله دارى.
I have almost the whole series.
من تقريبا درست.
I'm only missing Jack the Ripper and that Zodiac guy.
Ripper و آن مرد منطقه البروج.
But look.
ولي.
"The Black Widow."
"سياه."
It might be Debbie.
آن Debbie.
At least three rich husbands...
حد اقل شوهر دارايى...
all dead.
مرده همه.
I'll trade you.
من شما تجارت كرد.
For what?
What چه‌اى براي?
Amy Fischer.
.
Each year, we conclude our summer
Each سال., ما استنتاج مىكنيم صيف ما.
with a very special presentation.
مخصوص كاملا ارائه.
Book, music, and lyrics by...
موسيقي, و تصنيفهايى...
Gary Granger!
!
And this year,
و this year,
the old bean has come up with something pretty exciting--
لوبياى مسن آمده‌است. چيز مهم يا جالب برانگيزنده‌اى قشنگى --
my own personal salute to the first Thanksgiving.
شخصى. تا شكرگزاري.
Now, we have thought long and hard
ما اكنون انديشه كرده‌ايم. دراز و دشوار
about choosing just the right little actress
در حدود ناچيز صحيح تنها.
for the leading role of Sarah Miller,
براي نقش پيشرو آسيابان Sarah,
our beautiful and kindly pilgrim lady,
ما خوشگل و بانوى مهربانانه زائر,
and we have selected...
و ما...
Amanda Buckman!
!
And in the roles of her pilgrim pals--
و در نقشها Pals--
Lily, Jennifer, Tiffany, Missy,
Lily Jennifer, Tiffany خانم كوچولو,
Michelle, and Melissa!
Michelle و Melissa!
But, of course, not everyone can be a star.
ولي البته , Everyone ستاره‌اى.
Let's not forget our cheery little Chippewas
We Chippewas ناچيز شاد.
Mordecai, Yang,
.,
Esther...
Esther...
um...
Um...
Consuela, Irwin...
Consuela...
and, um...
و um...
I'm still not sure just how to pronounce this.
دادگر كه اين.
Jam-il?Jame-il?
Il?Jame-il?
[Gary] Jamal.
Gary Jamal.
Whatever.
.
And as their leader in the secondary
و مثل رهبر آنها ثانوى
but still compellingly written role of Pocahontas,
ولي خاموش نقش Pocahontas كتبى.,
guess who we have in mind.
ما در.
Our own little brunette outcast--
ناچيز Outcast سبزه.--
Wednesday Addams.
Wednesday Addams.
[Chimes Play Wedding March]
عروسي بازى ماه مارچ
We want to see Debbie and Fester.
ما مىخواهيم كه. Debbie و چرك.
Miss Debbie!
Debbie خطا بكن!
[Debbie] Debra!
Debbie Debra!
Gomez...
Gomez...
where are we?
آيا ما هستيم?
It looks familiar.
آن آشنا.
Of course-- the gates of hell.
البته -- دروازه‌ها جهنم.
Welcome to my home.
تا خانه‌ى من خوشامد بگو.
Might we see my brother?
ما برادر من را ببينيم?
No. He doesn't want to see any of you or that.
No. او نمىخواهد كه. هرى شما يا آن.
Why not?
چرا?
Because he's in love.
او در عشق.
He's wrapped in a gossamer blanket of ecstasy,
او تار عنكبوت پتو از خلسه.,
and he hates your guts.
و او روده‌هاى شما را متنفر است.
But why?
ولي چرا?
Because you've flaunted yourselves,
شما You,
your great love affair.
كار شما كلان عشق.
You kept him a child.
شما كودكى او نگاه داشتيد.
I've made him a man.
من مردى او ساخته‌ام.
Let me hear this from his own lips.
من اجازه بده اين بشنوم. لبان اذعان بدار.
His lips are busy.
لبان او مشغول هستند.
You want to talk to these people?
شما مىخواهيد كه. تا اينها مردمان?
Debbie.
Debbie.
Oh.
Oh.
Go away!
برو!
That is not my brother.
آن برادر من نيست.
Sorry.
متاسف.
You have enslaved him.
شما او.
placed Fester
چرك جاى داده شده‌است.
under some strange sexual spell.
برخى غريب جادوى جنسى.
I respect that. But, please, may we see him?
من آن بزرگ دارم. ولي ما او?
Don't even think about it.
تراز درباره آن انديشه بكن.
You have gone too far.
شما رفته‌ايد. دور too.
You have married Fester.
شما چرك ازدواج كرده.
You have destroyed his spirit.
روان او.
You have taken him from us.
شما او. ما.
All that I could forgive.
همه آن من ببخشايم.
But, Debbie...
ولي Debbie...
What?
What چه‌اى?
Pastels?
نقاشى پاستل يا گچ رنگى?
Get out of my house!
از خانه‌ى من به دست بآور!
Hit the road!
جاده را بزن!
And if you ever show your faces around here again,
و شما هميشه صورتهاى شما را از نو اينجا پيرامون نشان بده.,
I'll have you locked up for trying to visit.
من شما داشت كه.
Right, Fessie?
راست)
Right!
راست!
Luxor, nexor, burst, and burn!
لوكسور, nexor, بترک و بسوزان!
What is she doing?
او what چه‌اى?
Just a curse. Have a nice day.
دشنامى تنها. روز خوبى.
I demand justice!
من دادگسترى خواستار مىشوم!
Someone has married my brother.
كسى برادر من.
No.
No.
She took him to Hawaii.
او او تا هاوايى.
They have moved into a large, expensive home
آنها خانه‌ى.
where they make love constantly.
آنها عشق مىسازند. سطورمستمر.
I hate when that happens.
من آن روى مىدهد.
Arrest her at once without delay.
او يكبار بدون تاخير.
- Who? - Debbie.
- ? - Debbie.
My brother's wife, the temptress of Waikiki.
زن برادر من., Waikiki.
Who are you?
آيا شما هستيد?
What are you? Who moved the rock?
آيا شما what چه‌اى هستيد? آيا rock تكان داد?
Officer, you must issue a subpoena.
افسر., شما احضاريه‌اى صادر بكنيد.
I believe they own...
من اعتقاد دارم آنها اذعان دارند...
Gomez, no!
Gomez no!
A Buick!
Buick!
Just leave. Leave quietly. Leave now.
تنها رها بكن. به آرامى رها بكن. اكنون رها بكن.
Don't make me call Ringling Brothers.
من نساز صدا بكنم. برادران Ringling.
Has the planet gone mad?
آيا سياره ديوانه رفته‌است?
My brother... passion's hostage.
برادر من... گروگان اشتياق.
I seek justice.
من دادگسترى جستجو مىكنم.
Denied.
انكار كرده.
I shall not submit. I shall conquer. I shall rise.
من گردن نهاد. من فتح كرد. من.
My name is Gomez Addams, and I have seen evil!
نام من است., و من شر ديده‌ام!
I have seen horror!
من وحشت ديده شده‌است!
I have seen the unholy maggots
من ديده‌ام. حشرات unholy.
which feast in the dark recesses of the human soul!
Which در تاريكى مرخصى مىگيرد. جان ياروان انسانى!
They're at camp.
.
I have seen all this, Officer.
من all اين , افسر.
But until today,
ولي امروز، اين روزها ,
I had never seen...
من هرگز ديده‌بودم...
you!
شما!
Hook him, book him, cook him. Now!
او او, او پخته بشو. Now!
Next in line.
نزديك خط.
Yes, I'd like to renew my passport, please.
آرى, من متمايل بود كه گذرنانه‌ى من,.
I'll be leaving the country very shortly.
من كشور را رها كرد. بزودى كاملا.
Traveling alone?
به تنهايى?
Yes. I'll be a widow.
آرى. من بود.
♪ Happy, happy turkey day ♪
~ روز بوقلمون. ~
♪ Hunger pains will go away ♪
~ گرسنگى رفت  ~
♪ When you hear the pilgrims say ♪
~ شما. زائرها ~
♪ It's happy turkey day ♪
~ آن روز شاد بوقلمون  ~
♪ Happy, happy turkey day ♪
~ روز بوقلمون. ~
♪ Let's all eat the Indian way ♪
~ We all راه‌ى. ~
♪ As Bastille and Cape Cod day ♪
~ باستيل (زندان معروفى درپاريس) و روز  ~
♪ On happy turkey day ♪♪
~ روز شاد بوقلمون  ~~
Look at you. Oh, Amanda, you look perfect!
شما. شما كامل!
You're just the prettiest pilgrim I've ever seen!
شما زائر قشنگ تنها. من هميشه 've ديده‌ام!
Gar, come and take a look at this.
Gar و اين.
Here they are!
اينجا آنها!
They were by the phone.
آنها نزديك تلفن.
We were calling the FBI.
ما اداره پليس فدرال آمريكا.
Their uncle's in trouble.
در زحمت.
You're late for your fittings.
شما دير.
I don't want to be in the pageant.
من كه نمىخواهم. Pageant.
You won't help me realize my vision?
شما من بينايى من را?
Your work is puerile and under-dramatized.
شغل شما كودكانه است. و under-dramatized.
You lack any sense of structure, character,
شما هرى شعورى كم داريد. منش ,
or the Aristotelian unities.
يا وحدتها Aristotelian.
Young lady, I am getting just a tad tired
بانوى جوان., من دارم تنها tad به دست مىآورم خسته كرده.
of your attitude problem.
از مسئله‌ى شما رفتار.
Everyone, campers!
Everyone camper!
I have a wonderful idea.
من فكر شگرفى دارم.
Wednesday and Pugsley and young Mr. Glicker here,
Wednesday و Pugsley. و Glicker جوان اينجا ,
well, they have just never quite latched on
آنها تنها به تمامى هرگز
to the Chippewa spirit,
Chippewa روحيه بده.,
nor have some oftheir little comrades.
Nor برخى oftheir. رفيقهاى ناچيزى.
Isn't that sad?
آن ملول?
- Yes!
- بله!
Don't we just hate that?
ما دادگر آن?
- Yes!
- بله!
Don't we wish they'd just die?
آيا ما آرزو نمىكنيم? آنها مرد تنها?
- Yes!
- بله!
We don't.
ما.
But you know what we'll do with them?
ولي شما what چه‌اى ما آنها?
We're going to make an example.
ما داريم مىرويم كه. نمونه‌اى.
We are going to show that anyone,
آن هركس.,
no matter how odd or pale or chubby,
عجيب يا كمرنگ يا خپله,
can still have a darn good time.
داشت هنوز موقع خوبى.
Whether they like it or not.
آنها آن يا.
What are you going to do?
آيا شما داريد كه what چه‌اى مىرويد?
Yes, indeedy, just the ticket.
بله., بليط تنها.
Bambi.
Bambi.
Lassie Come Home.
Lassie.
The Little Mermaid.
ناچيز.
Stop it.
آن بييستان.
He's only a child.
او كودكى تنها.
Don't worry. We're getting out of here.
انديشناك نباش. ما out اينجا.
But...
ولي...
it's Disney.
آن Disney.
Yes.
آرى.
♪ The hillsare alive ♪
~  ~
♪ With the sound of music ♪
~ با صدا از موسيقي ~
♪ With songs they have sung ♪
~ آنها با آوازهايى آواز خوانده‌اند. ~
♪ For a thousand years... ♪♪
~ براي سالى... ~~
♪ And they knew that it was much more than a hunch ♪
~ و آنها آن More قوزى ~
♪ That this group must somehow form a family ♪
~ اين خانواده‌اى به طريقى تشكيل بده. ~
♪ That's the way we all became the BradyBunch... ♪♪
~ آن راه all ما BradyBunch... ~~
♪ You're always a day ♪
~ شما روزى هميشه. ~
♪ A-way ♪♪
~ A-way. ~~
Well...
فوران بكن...
good evening.
عصر به خير.
Is there anything you'd like to say to everyone?
آيا آنجا است? شما متمايل بود كه everyone?
Yes.
آرى.
And just what might that be?
و what چه‌اى تنها آن?
I'm not perky.
من perky.
That's for damn sure.
آن مطمئن.
But I want to be.
ولي من كه مىخواهم.
You do?
شما?
I want to smile
من مىخواهم كه.
and sing and dance
آواز بخوان و برقص.
and be Pocahontas in Gary's vision.
و Pocahontas در بينايى Gary.
Oh, darling, do you really mean it?
Oh عزيز, آيا شما آن واقعا قصد داريد?
- [Gasps]
-
Isn't she pretty?
او قشنگ?
She's scaring me!
او من!
Oh, Gar.
Oh.
Yeah.
Yeah.
Aah!
Aah!
Stay back!
پس!
He's very sick.
او بيمار كاملا.
My baby!
طفل من!
Lumbar, dison...
Lumbar...
pox and thither,
آبله و به آنجا,
curad, brattle,
Curad brattle,
bone and brine!
استخوان گوشت را در بآور و آب نمك بزن!
[Coos]
Coos
Well, he's stubborn.
او لجوج.
It works on cats.
آن بر گربه‌هايى كار مىكند.
- What are we going to do? - Is it hopeless?
- آيا ما داريم كه what چه‌اى مىرويم? - آيا آن نوميد است?
Here it is.
اينجا آن.
"Chapter 18. Infant possessions."
"فصل. 18. تصرفاتيى نوزاد."
He's possessed?
او تصاحب كرده?
"Warning signs--
"آگاهى امضاء مىكند.--
"severe alterations in appearance and personality.
"دگرگونيهاى سختى. ظهور و شخصيت.
Such alterations can become permanent."
دگرگونيهايى. جاودانى."
Permanent? Those golden curls?
جاودانى? آنها حلقه‌هاى طلايى?
Those rosy cheeks?
آنها گونه‌هاى گلگون?
That smile?
آن?
"These terrifying changes
"اينها تغييرات وحشت آزر.
"are most often the result of a troubled family life.
"برآمد غالبا most از زندگي زحمت داده شده‌است خانواده.
Separations--"
جدايىهايى.--"
You mean...
شما...
Fester!
!
Bingo! This kid knows
بينگو! اين بچه
that something is not right around here.
چيز مهم يا جالب راست اينجا پيرامون.
Unless Fester comes back, we're talking dimples.
پشتيبانى بكن مگر چرك مىآيد., ما دارند حرف مىزنند.
Not in this house.
در اين خانه.
He could stay this way for years. Forever.
او اين راه را برجا بماند. براي سالهايى. جاودانه.
He could become...
او...
a lawyer...
...
I won't listen!
من!
An orthodontist...
Orthodontist...
Mama, stop!
مامان,!
President.
رئيس.
[Pubert Laughs]
خنده‌هايى Pubert
Please! I beg you!
دلپذير بباش! من شما خواهش مىكنم!
Take me!
من!
Each summer we take this occasion
ما each صيف. اين فرصت.
to celebrate a seminal event in American history.
كه پيشامد بنيانىى. در تاريخ آمريكايىى.
This year, we depict
This year ما
perhaps the most important day in our shared past--
شايد most روز مهم در گذشته‌ى ما سهيم  بوده شده‌است --
the first Thanksgiving!
شكرگزاري!
A day for maize,
روزى براي ذرت.,
the Native American word for corn,
آمريكايى بومى. Word براي ذرت.,
a terrific turkey dinner,
شام ترس آدرى بوقلمون.,
and brotherhood!
و برادرى!
So, white meat and dark meat,
بنابراينى گوشت سفيدى و گوشت بي نور ,
take it away!
آن away!
[Piano Plays]
بازىهايى پيانو
♪ Eat us, hey, it's Thanksgiving day ♪
~ ما hey, آن روز شكرگزاري ~
♪ Eat us, we make a nice buffet ♪
~ ما بخور., ما بوفه‌ى خوبى مىسازيم. ~
♪ We lost the race with Farmer Ed ♪
~ ما مسابقه را گم كرديم. Ed ~
♪ Eat us 'cause we're good and dead ♪
~ ما ما خوب و مرده. ~
♪ White man or red man ♪
~ Man سفيد يا man سرخ. ~
♪ From East, North, or South ♪
~ از خاور, شمال, يا جنوب ~
♪ Chop off our legs ♪
~ از پاهاى ما تكه بكن. ~
♪ And put 'em in your mouth ♪
~ و گذاشته em در دهان شما  ~
♪ Eat me ♪
~ من بخور. ~
♪ Sauteed or barbecued ♪
~ Sauteed يا ~
♪ We once were pets, but now we're food ♪
~ ما يكبار بوديم., ولي now غذا  ~
♪ We won't stay fresh for very long ♪
~ ما بانشاط دراز كاملا  ~
♪ So eat us before we finish this song ♪
~ بنابراينى ما قبلا ما اين آواز را به پايان مىرسيم. ~
♪ Eat us before we finish this song ♪♪
~ ما قبلا بخور. ما اين آواز را به پايان مىرسيم. ~~
Thank you.
.
It was a senseless tragedy.
آن فاجعه‌ى بى شعورى بود.
Ha ha!
Ha!
Angel, I'm going out for just a minute.
فرشته, براي دقيقه‌اى تنها.
I forgot the champagne.
من شامپانى را فراموش كردم.
Our three-week anniversary! I'll go.
سالگرد ما هفته! من رفت.
No, no. You're working hard enough.
No no. شما.
I'll just put your present on the table.
من پيشكش شما گذاشت تنها. Table.
Don't peek!
دزدانه نگاه نكن!
Oh, please, please!
Oh لطفا
What is it?
آيا آن what چه‌اى است?
Is it string?
It نخ?
You never know.
شما هرگز.
Uh... is it a dog toy?
Uh... آيا آن بازيچه‌اى سگ است?
Just you wait.
دادگر شما.
It's a bomb.
آن بمبى.
What?
What چه‌اى?
I know. Wait for my birthday.
من. براي زادروز من صبر بكن.
Fester...
...
let me look at you.
من شما اجازه بده.
I want to remember you just this way.
من مىخواهم كه شما. اين راه تنها.
What do you mean?
آيا شما what چه‌اى قصد داريد?
Rich. Will you miss me?
دارا. شما من خطا كرد?
But you'll be right back, won't you?
ولي شما پس به سمت راست بود., شما?
Of course.
البته.
Whoo!
Whoo!
Hoo hoo hoo hoo!
Hoo!
I am so glad we invited the Chippewas
من شاد ما دعوت كرديم هستم. Chippewas.
to join us for this holiday meal.
كه ما. اين وعده غذا.
Remember, these savages are our guests.
اينها آدم بى تمدن مهمانهاى ما.
We must not be surprised
ما غافلگيرشده.
at any of their strange customs.
هرى آنها عادتهاى غريبى.
After all, they have not had our advantages,
All آنها برترىهاى ما را,
such as fine schools,
Such as مدرسه‌هاى خوبى,
libraries full of books,
كتابخانه‌هايى انباشته از كتابهايى.,
shampoo.
.
[Audience Chuckles]
Chuckle
How. I am Pocahontas, a Chippewa maiden.
. من Pocahontas هستم., دوشيزه‌اى Chippewa.
An Indian.
هندىى.
Enough said.
به اندازه كافى گفته.
And I am Running Bear,
و من,
betrothed to Pocahontas.
نامزد شده Pocahontas.
In the play.
در بازى.
20 grand for summer camp,
20 بزرگ براي صيف ,
he's Mr. Woo-Woo.
او Woo-Woo.
We have brought a special gift for this holiday feast.
ما مخصوصى آورده‌ايم. براي اين تعطيلى جشن بگير.
I am a turkey. Kill me.
من بوقلمونى هستم. من بكش.
What a thoughtful gift!
What چه‌اى چشم روشنى بافكرى!
Why, you are as civilized as we,
چرا شما متمدن كرده,
except we wear shoes and have last names.
ما كفشهايى و نامهاى آخرينى.
Welcome to our table, our new primitive friends.
Table خوشامد بگو., دوستان ما اوليه نو.
Thank you, Sarah Miller.
, آسيابان Sarah.
You're the most beautiful person I've ever seen.
شما most كس خوشگل. من هميشه 've ديده‌ام.
Your hair is the color of the sun,
موى شما رنگ است. از خورشيد,
your skin is like fresh milk,
پوست شما مانند شير بانشاطى است.,
and everyone loves you.
و everyone شما عاشق است.
Stop! Sit.
بييستان! بنشين.
Wait.
صبر بكن.
What?
What چه‌اى?
We cannot break bread with you.
ما بشكنيم. نان شما.
Huh? Becky, what's going on?
Huh? Becky., What چه‌اى?
[Becky] Wednesday!
Becky Wednesday!
You have taken the land
شما زمين را.
which is rightfully ours.
Which كدامى به حق.
Years from now, my people will be forced
سالهايى now., مردمان من اجبارى بود.
to live in mobile homes on reservations.
كه در خانه‌هاى سيارى. بر احتياطاتيى.
Your people will wear cardigans
مردمان شما. ژاكت پشمى پوشيد
and drink highballs.
و highball بنوش.
We will sell our bracelets by the roadsides.
ما النگوهاى ما را فروش رفت. حاشيه جاده.
You will play golf
شما بازى
and enjoy hot hors d'oeuvres.
و لذت ببر. Hors داغ d'oeuvres.
My people will have pain and degradation.
مردمان من درد داشت. و تنزل.
Your people will have stick shifts.
مردمان شما. تغييراتيى.
The gods of my tribe have spoken.
God از قبيله‌ى من. .
They have said, "Do not trust the pilgrims,
آنها, "زائرها را اعتماد ندار.,
especially Sarah Miller."
بخصوص آسيابان Sarah."
Gary, she's changing the words.
Gary او word.
And for all these reasons,
و براي all اينها عقلها ,
I have decided to scalp you
من تصميم گرفته‌ام كه شما.
and burn your village to the ground.
و روستاى شما را بسوزان. تا زمين.
[Yelling Indian War Cry]
ستيز
Aah!
Aah!
Children! Campers!
كودكان! Camper!
Stop! You're destroying my text!
بييستان! شما داريد متن من را ويران مىكنيد!
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah!
He's not a team player.
او بازيگرى تيم.
He needs friends.
او دوستان نياز دارد.
He needs friends like this?
او دوستان اين?
- Aah! - Oh!
- Aah! - Oh!
- [Gasps]
-
Aah!
Aah!
Uh, I beg your pardon.
Uh من بخشايش شما را.
Do something!
!
[Muffled Screams]
جيغهاى خاموش كرده شده‌اند
♪ Macho, macho man ♪
~ مرد. ~
♪ Feel my muscles ♪
~ Muscles احساس بكن. ~
♪ I've got to be a macho man ♪
~ من كه به دست آورده‌ام. ~
♪ Mucho, mucho, macho, macho ♪
~ Mucho ~
♪ I got to be a macho ♪
~ من شخص خشن و كه ~
♪ Hey, hey, hey, hey ♪
~ Hey ~
Hey! Wait! What time is it, Jorge?
Hey! صبر بكن! آيا آن) what چه است?
Ah, 6:25.
Ah 6:25.
Oops. Got to go.
Oops. كه.
- No! - Wait!
- No! - صبر بكن!
Wait here. It's my anniversary.
اينجا صبر بكن. آن سالگرد من.
I'll be right back.
من پس به سمت راست بود.
Your husband is a very lucky man.
شوهر شما. كاملا مرد lucky.
Don't say that!
آن نگو!
♪ Hey, hey, hey ♪
~ Hey ~
♪ Hey, macho, macho man ♪
~ Hey man ~
♪ I got to be a macho man ♪♪
~ من كه به دست آوردم. ~~
Cheers.
.
Oh, no, no.
Oh no no.
But, Officer...
ولي افسر...
my husband was in that house.
شوهر من. در آن خانه.
Happy anniversary, Debbie.
شاد سالگرد, Debbie.
Help. Help.
امداد. امداد.
Sweetheart! Did you get the champagne?
Sweetheart! آيا شما شامپانى را به دست آورديد?
Freeze!
يخ ببند!
Pookie?
Pookie?
I tried to make it look like an accident.
من سعي كردم كه آن. مانند تصادفى.
I tried to give you some dignity, but, oh, no, not you.
من سعي كردم كه شما., ولي no شما.
What are you saying?
آيا شما داريد what چه‌اى مىگويد?
I want you dead, and I want your money.
من مرده شما مىخواهم., و من پول شما را مىخواهم.
But--But... don't you love me?
But--But... آيا شما من عاشق نيستيد?
Is that a no?
آن no?
Oh, do I love you. Look at yourself!
Oh من شما. خود شما!
You're a nightmare. You're the missing link.
شما كابوسى. شما پيوند گمشده.
You shouldn't be married. You should be studied.
شما ازدواج كرده. شما تحصيل دانش كرده بشويد.
You're a big, dumb, weird thing.
بزرگ, چيز.
No woman in her right mind could love you.
No زنى در ذهن او صحيح. شما.
Yeow!
Yeow!
Thing!
چيز!
I'll get you! And your little hand, too!
من شما به دست آورد! و شما ناچيز
Aah!
Aah!
Come on.
.
No. I have to go back. For the others.
No. من (defective verb) كه. Other.
You're very brave.
شما دلير كاملا.
And to watch the place burn. You go.
و بسوزان كه محل را. شما مىرويد.
Save your uncle.
عموى شما را نجات بده.
I may never see you again.
من هرگز شما از نو ببين.
I know.
من.
There are forces tearing us apart--
هستند. ما apart.--
Gary, Debbie, seventh grade.
., .
I'll never forget you.
من شما هرگز فراموش كرد.
You won't?
شما?
You're too weird.
شما غريب too.
We'll always have today and Chippewa.
ما امروز،اين روزها داشت هميشه. و Chippewa.
And this.
و اين.
What is it?
آيا آن what چه‌اى است?
Amanda's retainer.
.
Cara mia.
Mia.
Mon cher.
Mon.
Come on!
!
Move it!
آن تكان بده!
Move out of the way!
از راه تكان بده!
"We looked,
"ما.,
"then we saw him step in on the mat.
"پس ما او ديديم. بر پادرى گام بزن.
"We looked, and we saw him--
"ما., و ما او ديديم.--
the cat in the hat."
گربه در مقام."
Are you enjoying this?
آيا شما داريد اين لذت مىبريد?
To think...
كه...
a child of mine.
كودكى.
"I know it is wet,
"من مىدانم آن تر است.,
"and the sun is not sunny,
"و خورشيد آفتاب رو نيست.,
"but we can have lots of good fun,
"ولي ما داشت. سرنوشتهايى از سرگرمى خوبى.,
that is funny."
آن بامزه است."
Oh, no.
Oh no.
He lives.
او زندگي مىكند.
Come on! It's Gomez!
! آن Gomez!
♪ Swing low ♪
~ پايين  ~
♪ Sweet chariot ♪
~ ارابه‌ى شيرين. ~
♪ Coming for to carry me home ♪
~ كه من. ~
♪ Swing low ♪♪
~ پايين  ~~
My baby is ill,
طفل من بيمار است.,
and my husband is dying.
و شوهر من .
Oh, mama, what shall I do?
Oh مامان , من what چه‌اى?
Well, you have a black dress.
شما لباس سياه‌اى.
Gomez!
Gomez!
- Fester!
- !
Fester? Where is Fester?
? آيا چرك است?
He's right here, mon cher.
او راست اينجا , Cher.
It's me, Gomez.
آن من Gomez.
I've tried to be someone I'm not.
من كه سعي كرده‌ام. كسى.
I live in shame...
من در شرم زندگي مىكنم...
and the suburbs!
و حومه‌ها!
But you belong to Debbie.
ولي شما Debbie تعلق داريد.
You're Debbie's love toy.
شما بازيچه‌ى Debbie عشق.
You are Mr. Debbie!
شما Debbie هستيد!
I am an Addams!
من Addams هستم!
Fester!
!
Uncle Fester!
چرك عمو!
Children!
كودكان!
You sent us to camp.
شما ما كه.
They made us sing.
آنها ما ساختند آواز مىخوانديم.
My own dear family.
خانواده‌ى من مال خود عزيز.
How I've missed you all.
من شما خطا كرده‌اند.
Our whole family-- together at last.
خانواده‌ى ما درست.-- باهم.
Three generations...
نسلى...
above ground.
بالا.
In-laws!
In-laws!
I don't want to hurt anybody.
من نمىخواهم. كه هركس.
I don't enjoy hurting anybody.
من لذت نمىبرم. هركس.
I don't like guns or bombs or electric chairs,
من توپهايى يا بمبهايى متمايل نيستم. يا صندلىهاى برقيى ,
but sometimes people just won't listen,
ولي بعضى اوقات مردمان تنها,
and so I have to use persuasion...
و بنابراينى من كه ...
and slides.
و.
My parents-- Sharon and Dave.
.-- Sharon و Dave.
Generous, doting...
...
or were they?
يا آنها?
All I ever wanted was a ballerina Barbie
All من هميشه خواستم. آيا Barbie بود?
in her pretty pink tutu.
Tutu صورتى قشنگ.
My birthday.
زادروز من.
I was 10,
من بودم.,
and do you know what they got me?
و شما آنها من?
Malibu Barbie.
.
The nightmare.
كابوس.
The nerve.
پى.
That's not what I wanted.
آن من what چه‌اى خواست.
That's not who I was.
آن I.
I was a ballerina--
من بودم.--
graceful, delicate.
.
They had to go.
آنها (defective verb) كه.
My first husband, the heart surgeon.
شوهر من., جراح قلب.
All day long, coronaries, transplants.
همه روز , Coronaries.
What about your needs?
What چه‌اى درباره نيازهاى شما?
"Sorry about dinner, Deb.
"متاسف در حدود شام, deb.
The pope has a cold."
Pope سرمايى دارد."
An axe.
تبرى.
That takes me back.
آن من back.
Husband number two-- the senator.
شوهر-- سناتور.
He loved his state. He loved his country.
او حالت او را عاشق بود. او كشور او را عاشق بود.
What about Debbie?
What چه‌اى Debbie?
"Sorry, Debbie. No Mercedes this year.
"متاسف Debbie. No Mercedes this year.
We have to set an example."
ما (defective verb) كه نمونه‌اى."
Oh, yeah? Set this!
Oh اين مستقر بشو!
My latest husband.
شوهر من دير.
My late husband Fester.
چرك من دير شوهر.
The fool.
ابله.
The corpse.
لاشه.
And his adorable family.
و خانواده‌ى او قابل پرستش.
You took me in. You accepted me.
شما من در. شما من پذيرفتيد.
But did any of you love me?
ولي آيا هرى شما من عاشق بوديد?
Really love me?
من واقعا?
Hands.
دستان.
So I--I killed.
I--I.
So I maimed.
بنابراينى من.
So I destroyed one innocent life after another.
من يك زندگي بي گناه.
Aren't I a human being?
من وجود انسانىى?
Don't I yearn and... ache and shop?
آيا من Don اشتياق ندارم و... و?
Don't I deserve love...
آيا من عشق Don استحقاق ندارم...
and jewelry?
و جواهر فروشى?
Adieu, mon cher.
Adieu.
Adios, cara mia.
Adios.
Debbie, let them go. Take me and my money.
Debbie آنها. من و پول من را.
For what I've done, I deserve to die.
من, من استحقاق دارم كه.
Sorry.
متاسف.
Goodbye, everybody.
خداحافظ هركس.
Wish me luck.
من بخت.
- Good luck.
- بخت خوب.
A birthday party! What a treat!
حزبى زادروز! What چه‌اى خوراك رايگان!
And to think I might have missed all this.
و كه من نيرو All اين.
What was I thinking of?
What چه‌اى من?
Physical pleasure.
خوشى جسمانى.
Oh...
Oh...
Uncle Fester, do you miss Debbie?
چرك عمو., آيا شما Debbie خطا مىكنيد?
Well, sometimes, late at night.
بعضى اوقات , دير شبانه.
I remember how she'd turn to me
من به ياد مىآورم. او من گرداند.
and say "Jesus, Fester, go back to your room."
و عيسى,, تا اتاق شما برو."
Yoo-hoo!
Yoo-hoo!
Are we late?
آيا ما دير هستيم?
Not at all. We'rejust getting started.
به هيچوجه. We'rejust.
I hope no one minds. We brought along a guest.
من انتظار دارم no one مواظبت نمىكند. ما along مهمانى.
This is our new nanny-- Dementia.
اين پرستار ما نو است.-- Dementia.
Oh...
Oh...
What a beautiful name.
What چه‌اى نام خوشگلى.
It means insanity.
آن جنون قصد دارد.
My name's Fester. It means to rot.
چرك نام من. آن قصد دارد كه.
A toast.
.
To the glorious mysteries of life.
باشكوه رازهايى زندگي.
To all that binds a family as one.
All آن خانواده‌اى.
To mirth, to merriment, to manslaughter.
تا خوشى, تا نشاط, آدمكشي غيرعمد.
- Hear, hear. - [Chattering]
- . -
To dear friends.
تا دوستان عزيزى.
To new friends.
تا دوستان نويى.
To youth.
تا جوان.
How do I look?
من?
Disturbing.
.
To passion.
اشتياق.
To paradise.
بهشت.
To pain.
كه.
Tonight.
امشب.
Ha ha! Make way for the birthday boy!
Ha! راه براي پسر زادروز!
Thing, will you do the honors?
چيز, will شما ?
[Playing "Happy Birthday"]
زادروز شاد
Your family is really interesting.
خانواده‌ى شما. جالب واقعا.
Your parents are so involved with each other.
پدريا مادر بنابراينى درگير همديگر.
Wednesday, do you think, like, maybe someday
Wednesday شما , شايد روزى
you might want to get married and have kids?
شما بخواهيد كه. ازدواج كرده و بچه‌هايى?
No.
No.
But what if you met just the right man
ولي what چه‌اى شما Man صحيح تنها.
who worshipped and adored you,
عبادت كرد. و شما ,
who'd do anything for you,
هرچيز. شما ,
who'd be your devoted slave?
بود برده‌ى شما وقف كرده شده‌است?
What would you do?
شما what چه‌اى?
I'd pity him.
من او دلسوزي كرد.
Poor Debbie. She was sick.
Debbie بي پول. او بيمار بود.
She wasn't sick.
او بيمار.
She was sloppy.
او شلخته بود.
What do you mean?
آيا شما what چه‌اى قصد داريد?
If I wanted to kill my husband, I'd do it, and I wouldn't get caught.
من خواست كه شوهر من را., من آن و من قاپيده شده‌ام به دست آورد.
How?
?
I'd scare him to death.
من او death ترساند.
No, you wouldn't.
No شما.
We're all very sorry, Debbie.
Debbie.
We wish you only the best.
ما شما تنها بهترين.
Aah! Aah!
Aah! Aah!
Aah!
Aah!
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Come on, come on ♪
~  ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Yeah, yo, dig it ♪
~ Yeah آن ~
♪ Back again, the Addams Family ♪
~ از نو پشتيبانى بكن., خانواده Addams. ~
♪ New baby in the house makes three ♪
~ طفل در خانه نو. ~
♪ Wednesday, Pugsley, Lurch, you ring it ♪
~ Wednesday Pugsley, دام, شما آن ~
♪ Fester, Grandmama, and Thing ♪
~ Grandmama, و چيز  ~
♪ Wait, can't forget cousin Itt ♪
~ انتظار, دخترعمو Itt ~
♪ Tag team raps another party hit ♪
~ ضربه‌هايى تيم برچسب بزن. حزب زد. ~
♪ It's the Addams Family movie thing ♪
~ آن خانواده Addams چيز سينما. ~
♪ Gomez, Morticia, come on, sing ♪
~ ., ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Come on, come on ♪
~  ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Let me tell you, it's the A-D-D-A-M-S ♪
~ من اجازه بده شما بگوم., آن A-D-D-A-M-S ~
♪ The Addams Family, y'all, yes, yes ♪
~ خانواده Addams., Y'all آرى, بله  ~
♪ They're creepy, kooky, mysterious, spooky ♪
~ Kooky, اسرار آميز spooky ~
♪ As loony as can be when you see the movie ♪
~ خل و ديوانه شما سينما را مىبيند. ~
♪ It goes on and on, the madness won't stop ♪
~ آن و , ديوانگي  ~
♪ Tick to the tock around the clock ♪
~ Tock علامت بگذار. نزديك به ساعت ~
♪ Tag team kicks the floor, really, though ♪
~ تيم برچسب طبقه را, واقعا گرچه ~
♪ With the Addams Family, so here we go ♪
~ با خانواده Addams, ما اينجا  ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Hey, there it is ♪
~ Hey آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Come on, come on, come on, come on ♪
~ , ~
♪ Whoomp! Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده. ~
♪ Whoomp! Family, whoa ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده, whoa ~
♪ The Addams Family ♪
~ خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Something's strange, something's funny ♪
~ غريب, بامزه  ~
♪ Nanny's got a plot to get the family money ♪
~ پرستار توطئه‌اى كه پول را خانواده. ~
♪ Makes Fester fall for her ♪
~ او پائين بيا. ~
♪ Thing gets wise, spreads the word ♪
~ چيز دانا, Word ~
♪ The family comes to Fester's aid ♪
~ خانواده. تا كمك چرك  ~
♪ The plot is foiled, no one gets paid ♪
~ توطئه دفع كرده مىشود., No one پرداخت كرده شده‌است به دست نمىآورد. ~
♪ It's the Addams Family runnin' things ♪
~ آن خانواده Addams Runnin چيزهايى  ~
♪ Get back while tag team swings ♪
~ به دست بآور. لحظه نوساناتيى تيم  ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Yeah, come on, come on ♪
~ Yeah ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Yeah, give it to me ♪
~ Yeah آن من ~
♪ It's a family thing, and it won't quit ♪
~ آن چيزى خانواده , و آن ترك كرده ~
♪ They keep it together, y'all, and that's it ♪
~ آنها آن نگاه دارند., Y'all و آن it ~
♪ They're not ordinary, just strange ♪
~ آنها معمولى., غريب تنها ~
♪ Some say loco, insane to the brain ♪
~ برخى كم عقل , ديوانه تا مغز  ~
♪ But you know that you love 'em ♪
~ ولي شما آن شما em ~
♪ In a class by theirselves ♪
~ در طبقه‌اى Theirselves ~
♪ None below, none above 'em ♪
~ هيچى., هيچى em ~
♪ It ain't nothing to be ashamed of♪
~ آن كه شرمنده~
♪ So give love to the folks who go by the name of♪
~ بنابراينى عشق folks نزديك نام ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Yeah ♪
~ Yeah. ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Ooh-ee ♪
~ Ee. ~
♪ The Addams Family Theme, I'm gonna kick it ♪
~ زمينه خانواده Addams., Gonna آن ~
♪ Step to the mic like Cube and get with it ♪
~ Mic گام بزن. و با آن ~
♪ Props to the number one family of horror ♪
~ يك تا عدد خانواده وحشت ~
♪ This song's for the movie and the dance floor ♪
~ براي سينما و رقص  ~
♪ Tag team always delivers the funk ♪
~ تيم برچسب. Funk هميشه  ~
♪ From the old school, with the bump for the trunk ♪
~ از مدرسه‌ى مسن , دست انداز براي بدنه ~
♪ And it umps, with big bass on the low ♪
~ و آن umps, صداى بم در اپرا پايين بزرگى  ~
♪ Like my homey all said ♪
~ All homey ~
♪ You don't hear me, though ♪
~ شما من گرچه ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Yeah, give it to me ♪
~ Yeah آن من ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ Yeah ♪
~ Yeah. ~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~~
♪ Express yourself♪
~ خود شما بيان بكن.~
♪ Ooh ♪
~ Ooh. ~
♪ You don't ever need help from nobody else ♪
~ شما هميشه امداد nobody else. ~
♪ All you've got to do now, yeah ♪
~ All شما كه به دست آورده‌ايد. اكنون. ~
♪ Come on ♪
~  ~
♪ Express yourself, come on ♪
~ خود شما بيان بكن., ~
♪ Let it out of its creepy shell ♪
~ آن اجازه بده. از لاك آن چندش آور  ~
♪ Because you know you could ♪
~ شما شما  ~
♪ Express yourself, come on ♪
~ خود شما بيان بكن., ~
♪ Come on, people Come on, people ♪
~ مردمان مردمان ~
♪ 'Cause you know it's good, yeah ♪
~ 'سبب شما مىدانيد. آن خوب yeah ~
♪ Express yourself♪♪
~ خود شما بيان بكن.~~
♪ Breaking hearts ♪
~ قلبهايى breaking. ~
♪Just ain't my day ♪
~ ~
♪ It ain't my day ♪
~ آن ~
♪ All I want to do ♪
~ All من كه مىخواهم. ~
♪ Is love you ♪
~ شما  ~
♪ Well ♪
~ فوران بكن. ~
♪ Sugar, I won't fill ya ♪
~ شكر, من ya ~
♪ With regret, my love ♪
~ با افسوس, عشق من ~
♪ Yo, what you're lookin' for ♪
~ Yo what چه‌اى  ~
♪ Is real lovin' ♪
~ Lovin واقعى ' ~
♪ Real lovin' ♪
~ Lovin واقعى.' ~
♪ No matter what you see ♪
~ شما  ~
♪ Ahh, baby ♪
~ Ahh طفل  ~
♪ What you see ♪
~ شما what چه‌اى مىبيند. ~
♪ Yeah, is what you get ♪
~ Yeah شما  ~
♪ Is what you get ♪
~ شما  ~
♪ What you see ♪
~ شما what چه‌اى مىبيند. ~
♪ I said what you see ♪
~ من گفتم. ~
♪ Is what you get, now, baby ♪
~ شما now طفل  ~
♪ Is what you get ♪
~ شما  ~
♪ And real ♪
~ و واقعى  ~
♪ And the real thing ♪
~ و چيز واقعى  ~
♪ Is the best thing yet ♪
~ چيز بهترين هنوز ~
♪ Oh ♪
~ Oh. ~
♪ Oh, what you see ♪
~ Oh شما  ~
♪ Yes, why ♪
~ آرى, چرا  ~
♪ Is what you get ♪
~ شما  ~
♪ Oh, oh ♪
~ Oh oh ~
♪ You're so good ♪
~ شما خوب. ~
♪ I can't stand myself♪
~ من خودم بايستم.~
♪ Ah, ah, ah ♪
~ Ah ~
♪ Is what you get ♪
~ شما  ~
♪ Ooh, baby ♪
~ Ooh طفل  ~
♪ What you see ♪
~ شما what چه‌اى مىبيند. ~
♪ Is what you get ♪
~ شما  ~
♪ I said what you see ♪
~ من گفتم. ~
♪ Is what you get, now, baby ♪
~ شما now طفل  ~
♪ Is what you get ♪
~ شما  ~
♪ And real ♪
~ و واقعى  ~
♪ Is the best thing yet ♪
~ چيز بهترين هنوز ~
♪ Are you ready for me? ♪
~ آيا شما آماده من هستيد? ~
♪ Whoo! ♪♪
~ Whoo! ~~
♪ Do it, do it any way you wanna do it ♪
~ آن آن هرى راه‌اى شما wanna آن ~
♪ Do it any way you wanna ♪
~ آن هرى راه‌اى شما. ~
♪ I saw you ♪
~ من شما ديدم. ~
♪ Do it any way you wanna do it ♪
~ آن هرى راه‌اى. شما wanna آن ~
♪ Do it any way you wanna ♪
~ آن هرى راه‌اى شما. ~
♪ I saw you, baby ♪
~ من شما طفل  ~
♪ Do it ♪
~ آن. ~
♪ Do it any way you wanna ♪
~ آن هرى راه‌اى شما. ~
♪ Do it any way you wanna, wanna, wanna ♪♪
~ آن هرى راه‌اى. شما wanna ~~
♪ Whoomp! Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
♪ There it is ♪
~ آنجا آن ~
♪ Whoomp! The Addams Family ♪
~ Whoomp! خانواده Addams. ~
The Addams Family ♫
خانواده Addams. ~~